<idea-plugin version="2">
    <name>SyncEdit 2</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
    This is version 2.0 of the original SyncEdit plugin created by Nathan Brown.  It has not been updated since 2006 and has
    not worked cleanly since IntelliJ IDEA version 9. I have attempted to manually patch it and get it working again.  I hope
    to add additional features and functionality but for now it is just an updated release of the original code.  The first
    version had no published license and numerous attempts at contacting the auther went unanswered so I have simply cloned
    it and am releasing it as an open source version 2.0.

    This plugin allows you to do an inplace synchronized edit of all instances of a string within a defined range.<br><br>

    A "SyncEdit Mode" menu item is added to the Search and Editor Popup menus.  Simply select a range to be edited,
    enter "SyncEdit Mode" and all words in the marked range become 'live' - any changes to an instance of a word changes
    all matching strings in real-time.<br><br>

    When in SyncEdit mode, pressing TAB/Ctrl+TAB will take you forward to the next/previous SyncEditable word found, respectively.<br><br>

    The decision about the word to SyncEdit is determined by a 'Select Word' type operation at the current cursor location
    (respecting any CamelHump settings) when a modification is made. However, you can SyncEdit a custom region of text by
    first selecting it and then invoking the SyncEdit action again, or even just start typing to replace the substring
    completely.<br><br>

    There is also a "Paste with SyncEdit" action added to the Edit Menu - this will execute a paste and automatically
    enter SyncEdit Mode for the range of the pasted text, great for tweaking pasted code fragments for the context they
    are used in.<br><br>

    The mode can be exited by pressing either escape or enter - once to exit SyncEdit on a word, and once again to stop
    SyncEditing a range.  The colours used by the SyncEdit plugin can be customised on the Plugins tab of the editor
    Colors & Fonts settings.<br><br>

    Known Issues:
    - While syncediting, the delete key does not behave correctly if you are not focused on the initial occurrence of
    the text being changed.
    - Some text that should not be selected within the range still gets changed;  not sure how to repeat this issue yet.
    ]]>
    </description>
    <version>2.0</version>
    <vendor email="billdwhite@gmail.com">Bill White</vendor>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
    2.0 - Changing version to correspond with name
    1.0 - Initial version directly built upon SyncEdit originally created by Nathan Brown (abandoned since 2006)
    ]]>
    </change-notes>
    <idea-version since-build="123.94"/>
    <application-components>
        <component>
            <implementation-class>org.ideaplugins.syncedit.SyncEditApplicationComponent</implementation-class>
        </component>
    </application-components>
    <project-components>
        <component>
            <implementation-class>org.ideaplugins.syncedit.SyncEditProjectComponent</implementation-class>
        </component>
    </project-components>
    <actions>
        <action id="SyncEditModeAction"
                class="org.ideaplugins.syncedit.SyncEditModeAction"
                text="SyncEdit Mode"
                description="Activate SyncEdit Mode">
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default"
                               first-keystroke="ctrl alt R"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu"
                          anchor="after"
                          relative-to-action="RefactoringMenu"/>
        </action>
        <action id="SyncEditModePasteAction"
                class="org.ideaplugins.syncedit.SyncEditModePasteAction"
                text="Paste with SyncEdit"
                description="Execute a paste, setting SyncEdit mode on the pasted block">
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default"
                               first-keystroke="ctrl alt INSERT"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="CutCopyPasteGroup"
                          anchor="after"
                          relative-to-action="EditorPasteSimple"/>
        </action>
        <action id="PreviousSyncEditableWordAction"
                class="org.ideaplugins.syncedit.PreviousSyncEditableWordAction"
                text="Previous SyncEditable Word"
                description="Selects the previous SyncEditable word when in SyncEdit Mode">
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default"
                               first-keystroke="ctrl TAB"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorActions"
                          anchor="last"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="GoToMenu"
                          anchor="after"
                          relative-to-action="GotoPreviousTodo"/>
        </action>
        <action id="NextSyncEditableWordAction"
                class="org.ideaplugins.syncedit.NextSyncEditableWordAction"
                text="Next SyncEditable Word"
                description="Selects the next SyncEditable word when in SyncEdit Mode">
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default"
                               first-keystroke="TAB"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorActions"
                          anchor="last"/>
            <add-to-group group-id="GoToMenu"
                          anchor="after"
                          relative-to-action="PreviousSyncEditableWordAction"/>
        </action>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>